Finding aid for News and Information Services (University of Michigan) records, 1900-[ongoing]
Bentley Historical Library
- Topical files
  - 1971
    - Linguistics, 1971 (Box 37)
    - LSA, 1971 (Box 37)
    - Mathematics (LSA), 1971 (Box 37)
    - Mechanical Engineering (Box 37)
    - Medical School (Box 37)
    - Mental Health Research Institute, 1971 (Box 37)
    - Mental Retardation, Institute for the Study of, 1971 (Box 37)
    - Meteorology and Oceanography, 1971 (Box 37)
    - Michigan Historical Collections (Box 38)
    - Michigan Men's Glee Club, 1971 (Box 38)
    - Michigan Union (Box 38)
    - Minority Groups (Box 38)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 38)
    - Museum of Anthropology, 1971 (Box 38)
    - Museum of Art, 1971_ (Box 38)
    - Museum of Zoology, 1971 (Box 38)
    - Music, School of, 1971 (Box 38)
    - Natural Resources, School of, 1971 (Box 38)
    - Naval Architecture and Marine Engineering, 1971 (Box 38)
    - Navy Officer Education Program, 1971 (Box 38)
    - Near Eastern and North African Studies, Center for, 1971 (Box 38)
    - Nuclear Engineering, 1971 (Box 38)
    - Nursing, School of, 1971 (Box 38)
    - Ophthalmology, 1971 (Box 38)
    - Opportunity Award Program, 1971 (Box 38)
    - Otorhinolaryngology, 1971 (Box 38)
    - Pathology, 1971 (Box 38)
    - Pediatrics and communicable diseases, 1971 (Box 38)
    - Personne1, 1971 (Box 38)
    - Pharmacology, 1971 (Box 38)
    - Pharmacy, College of, 1971 (Box 38)
    - Phoenix Project (Box 38)
    - Physical Education, 1971 (Box 38)
    - Physical Properties, 1971 (Box 38)
    - Physics (LSA), 1971 (Box 38)
    - Placement Services, 1971 (Box 38)
    - Political Science (LSA), 1971 (Box 38)
    - Political Studies, Center for Research on, 1971 (Box 38)
    - Population Planning, Center for, 1971 (Box 38)
    - Postgraduate medicine P, 1971 (Box 38)
    - President, Office of the, 1971 (Box 38)
    - Professional and Administrative Staff Services, Office of, 1971 (Box 38)
    - Professional Theatre Program (Box 38)
    - Psychiatry, 1971 (Box 38)
    - Psychology (LSA), 1971 (Box 38)
    - Public Health, School of, 1971 (Box 38)
    - Public Policy Studies, Institute of, 1971 (Box 38)
    - Recruitment (Box 38)
    - Regents, Board of, 2 folders (Box 38)
    - Registrar, Office of the, 1971 (Box 38)
    - Registration and Records, 1970 (Box 38)
    - Religious Affairs, Office of, 1971 (Box 38)
    - Research, Office of the Vice President for, 1971 (Box 38)
    - Research Administration, 1971 (Box 38)
    - Residential College, 1971 (Box 38)
    - Romance Languages and Literatures (LSA), 1971 (Box 38)
    - ROTC, 1971 (Box 38)
    - Russel (Henry) Lectures and Awards, 1971 (Box 38)
    - Russian and East European Studies, Center for, 1971 (Box 38)
    - Science and Technology, Institute of, 1971 (Box 38)
    - Sea Grant Program (Box 38)
    - Security Offices, 1971 (Box 38)
    - Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs, 1971 (Box 38)
    - Senate Assembly (Box 38)
    - Simpson Memorial Institute, 1971 (Box 38)
    - Student Affairs (Box 38)
    - TV Center (Box 38)
    - University Housing (Box 38)
    - University Musical Society, 1971 (Box 38)
    - U-M (general) (Box 38)
    - U-M Press, 2 folders (Box 38)
    - University Relations, 1971 (Box 38)
  - 1972 (Box 39)
    - Academic Affairs, Office of the Vice President (Box 39)
    - Admissions, Office of (Undergraduate) (Box 39)
    - Aerospace Engineering Department (Box 39)
    - Afro-American and African Studies (Box 39)
    - Alumni Association (Box 39)
    - Anatomy (Med.) (Box 39)
    - Anthropology (LSA) (Box 39)
    - Appropriations (Box 39)
    - Architecture and Design, College of (Box 39)
    - Argonne University Association (Box 39)
    - Army Officer Education Program (Box 39)
    - Art (Box 39)
    - Astronomy (LSA) (Box 39)
    - Automotive Engineering Lab (Box 39)
    - Bands (Box 39)
    - Bio-Sciences (Box 39)
    - Biological Station (Box 39)
    - Botanical Gardens (Box 39)
    - Budget (Box 39)
    - Buildings (Box 39)
    - Business Administration, School of (Box 39)
    - Business Research, Bureau of (Box 39)
    - Chemistry (LSA)
      - General (Box 39)
      - Mark Green Case (Box 39)
    - Chinese Ping Pong Team Visit (Box 39)
    - Chinese Studies, Center for (Box 39)
    - Civil Engineering (Box 39)
    - Clements Library, William L. (Box 39)
    - Commencement (Box 39)
    - Commission on Women (Box 39)
    - Committee on Institutional Cooperation (Box 39)
    - Computing Center (Box 39)
    - Continuing Education of Women, Center for (Box 39)
    - Continuing Engineering Education (Box 39)
    - Continuing Legal Education, Institute of (Box 39)
    - Cook, W.W. Lectures (Box 39)
    - Dearborn Campus (Box 39)
    - Dentistry, School of (Box 39)
    - Dental Research Institute (Box 39)
    - Dermatology (Med.) (Box 39)
    - Development Office (Box 39)
    - Economics (LSA) (Box 39)
    - Education, School of (Box 39)
    - Electrical Engineering, 1972 (Box 39)
    - Engineering, College of (Box 39)
    - English (LSA) (Box 39)
    - English Language Institute (Box 39)
    - Enrollment (Box 39)
    - Environmental Quality, Institute of (Box 39)
    - Exhibit Museum (Box 39)
    - Extension Service (Box 39)
    - Faculty (Box 39)
    - Fees (Box 39)
    - Financial (Box 40)
    - Financial Aid, Student, Office of (Box 40)
    - Flint College (Box 40)
    - Geology and Mineralogy (LSA) (Box 40)
    - Gerontology, Institute of (Box 40)
    - Graduate Studies, Horace H. Rackham School of (Box 40)
    - Grants and Contracts (State, Federal) (Box 40)
    - Great Lakes Research Division (Box 40)
    - Highway Safety Research Institute (Box 40)
    - History (LSA) (Box 40)
    - History of Art (LSA) (Box 40)
    - Holden Perinatal Research Laboratories (Box 40)
    - Honors
      - (Faculty) (Box 40)
      - (Student) (Box 40)
    - Hopwood Awards (Box 40)
    - Human Genetics (Med.) (Box 40)
    - Industrial Development Division (Box 40)
    - Information Services (Box 40)
    - Intercollegiate Athletics (Box 40)
    - Journalism (LSA) (Box 40)
    - Judiciary (Box 40)
    - Kelsey Museum of Ancient and Medieval Archaeology (Box 40)
    - Law School (Box 40)
    - Learning and Teaching, Center for Research on (Box 40)
    - Libraries (Box 40)
    - Literature, Science and the Arts, College of, 4 folders (Box 40)
    - Management Education, Division of (Box 40)
    - Mechanical Engineering (Box 40)
    - Medical School, 3 folders (Box 40)
    - Mental Health Research Institute (Box 40)
    - Mental Retardation, Institute for the Study of (Box 40)
    - Meteorology and Oceanography (Box 40)
    - Michigan Education Research Triad (MERIT) (Box 40)
    - Michigan Historical Collections (Box 40)
    - Minority Groups (Box 40)
    - Museum of Anthropology (Box 40)
    - Museum of Art (Box 40)
    - Music, School of (Box 40)
    - Natural Resources, School of (Box 40)
    - Opportunity Award Program (Box 40)
    - Personnel (Box 40)
    - Pharmacy, College of (Box 40)
    - Physical Education (Box 40)
    - Physics (Box 40)
    - Physiology (Med.) (Box 40)
    - Placement Services (Box 40)
    - Political Science (Box 40)
    - Postgraduate Medicine (Box 40)
    - Psychiatry (Box 40)
    - Psychology (LSA) (Box 40)
    - Public Health, School of (Box 40)
    - Regents, 3 folders (Box 41)
    - Registrar, Office of the (Box 41)
    - Religious Affairs, Office of (Box 41)
    - Research, Office of the Vice-President (Box 41)
    - Research Administration, Office of Associate Director (Box 41)
    - Residential College (Box 41)
    - ROTC (General) (Box 41)
    - Russel, Henry, Lecture Awards (Box 41)
    - Science and Technology, Institute of (Box 41)
    - Sea Grant Program (Box 41)
    - Security Offices (Box 41)
    - Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs (Box 41)
    - Slavic languages and Literatures (Box 41)
    - Social Research, Institute for (Box 41)
    - Social Work, School of (Box 41)
    - State and Community Relations (Box 41)
    - State Relations and Planning (Box 41)
    - Student Services, Office of, 2 folders (Box 41)
    - Student Organizations, Office of (Box 41)
    - Survey Research Center (Box 41)
    - Television Center (Box 41)
    - Unions (Box 41)
    - University Housing, 3 folders (Box 41)
    - University Musical Society (Box 41)
    - University of Michigan (General) (Box 41)
    - University of Michigan Press (Box 41)
    - University Relations (Box 41)
    - University Theatre Program (Box 41)
    - Women-Affirmative Action Program, 2 folders (Box 41)
    - WUOM Radio Station (Box 41)
  - 1973
    - Academic Affairs (Box 42)
    - Admissions, Office of (Undergraduate) (Box 42)
    - Aerospace Engineering Department (Box 42)
    - Afro-American and African Studies (Box 42)
    - Aging Conference (Box 42)
    - Air Force officers Education Program (Box 42)
    - Alumni Association (Box 42)
    - Anatomy (Med.) (Box 42)
    - Anthropology (LSA) (Box 42)
    - Applied Mechanics of Engineering Science (Box 42)
    - Appropriations (Box 42)
    - Architecture and Design, College of (Box 42)
    - Argonne University Association (Box 42)
    - Art (Box 42)
    - Asian Studies (Box 42)
    - Astronomy (LSA) (Box 42)
    - Athletics (Box 42)
    - Atmospheric and Oceanic Science (Box 42)
    - Automotive Engineering Lab (Box 42)
    - Bands (Box 42)
    - Biological Chemistry (Box 42)
    - Bio-Sciences (Box 42)
    - Biological Station (Box 42)
    - Botanical Gardens (Box 42)
    - Budget (Box 42)
    - Buildings (Box 42)
    - Business Administration, School of (Box 42)
    - Career Planning and Placement (Box 43)
    - Chemical Engineering (Box 43)
    - Chemistry (LSA)
      - General (Box 43)
    - Chinese Studies, Center for (Box 43)
    - Civil Engineering (Box 43)
    - Clements Library, William L (Box 43)
    - Commencement (Box 43)
    - Commission on Women (Box 43)
    - Committee on Institutional Cooperation (Box 43)
    - Committees (University wide) (Box 43)
    - Continuing Education of Women, Center for (Box 43)
    - Continuing Engineering Education (Box 43)
    - Continuing Legal Education, Institute of (Box 43)
    - Cooley (Thomas) Lectures (Box 43)
    - Dearborn Campus (Box 43)
    - Dentistry, School of (Box 43)
    - Development Office (Box 43)
    - Early Childhood Development and Education, Center for (Box 43)
    - Economic Development, Center for Research on (Box 43)
    - Economics (LSA) (Box 43)
    - Education, School of (Box 43)
    - Electrical and Computer Engineering (Box 43)
    - Engineering, College of English (LSA) (Box 43)
    - English Language Institute Enrollment (Box 43)
    - Environmental Quality, Institute of (Box 43)
    - Epidemiology (Box 43)
    - Ethics and Religion, Office of (Box 43)
    - Exhibit Museum (Box 43)
    - Extension Service (Box 43)
    - Faculty (Box 43)
    - Fees (Box 43)
    - Financial (Box 43)
    - Financial Aid, Student, Office of (Box 44)
    - Flint College (Box 44)
    - Geography (LSA) (Box 44)
    - Geological Science (Box 44)
    - Germanic Languages and Literatures (LSA) (Box 44)
    - Gerontology, Institute of (Box 44)
    - Graduate Studies, Horace H. Rackham School of (Box 44)
    - Grants and Contracts (Private foundation) (Box 44)
    - Great Lakes Research Division (Box 44)
    - Health Service (Box 44)
    - Higher Education, Center for the Study of (Box 44)
    - Highway Safety Research Institute (Box 44)
    - History (LSA) (Box 44)
    - History of Art (LSA) (Box 44)
    - Hometown Stories (Box 44)
    - Honors
      - (Faculty) (Box 44)
      - (Student) (Box 44)
    - Honors Council (LSA) (Box 44)
    - Hopwood Awards (Box 44)
    - Hospital Administration, Bureau of and Program in (Box 44)
    - Industrial Development Division (Box 44)
    - Industrial and Operations Engineering (Box 44)
    - Information Services (Box 44)
    - International Center (Box 44)
    - Journalism (LSA) (Box 44)
    - Kelsey Museum of Ancient and Medieval Archaeology (Box 44)
    - Labor and Industrial Relations (Box 44)
    - Law School (Box 44)
    - Learning and Teaching, Center for Research on (Box 44)
    - Library Science, School of (Box 44)
    - Literature, Science and the Arts, College of, 2 folders (Box 44)
    - Mathematics (LSA) (Box 44)
    - Mechanical Engineering (Box 44)
    - Media Resources (Box 44)
    - Medical School, 3 folders (Box 44)
    - Mental Health Research Institute (Box 44)
    - Mental Retardation, Institute for the Study of (Box 44)
    - Michigan Historical Collections (Box 44)
    - Michigan League (Box 44)
    - Michigan Men's Glee Club (Box 44)
    - Minority Groups (Box 44)
    - Museum of Anthropology (Box 44)
    - Museum of Art (Box 44)
    - Museum of Zoology (Box 44)
    - Music, School of (Box 44)
    - Natural Resources, School of (Box 45)
    - Naval Officer Education Program (Box 45)
    - Near Eastern and North African Studies, Center for (Box 45)
    - Neuropsychiatric Institute (Box 45)
    - Nuclear Engineering (Box 45)
    - Nursing, School of (Box 45)
    - Obstetrics and Gynecology (Box 45)
    - Opportunity Award Program (Box 45)
    - Orientation, Office of (Box 45)
    - Pathology (Box 45)
    - Personnel (Box 45)
    - Pharmacology (Box 45)
    - Physical Education (Box 45)
    - Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation (Box 45)
    - Physical Properties, Department of (Box 45)
    - Physics (Box 45)
    - Political Science (Box 45)
    - Political Studies, Center for (ISR) (Box 45)
    - Population Studies Center (Box 45)
    - Professional and Administrative Staff Services, Office of (Box 45)
    - Psychology (LSA) (Box 45)
    - Public Health, School of (Box 45)
    - Public Policy Studies, Institute of (Box 45)
    - Regents (Box 45)
    - Registrar, Office of the (Box 45)
    - Research, Office of the Vice-President (Box 45)
    - Research Development and Administration, Division of, 2 folders (Box 45)
    - Residential College (Box 45)
    - ROTC (General) (Box 45)
    - Russel, Henry, Lecture Awards (Box 45)
    - Russian and East European Studies, Center for (Box 45)
    - Science and Technology, Institute of (Box 45)
    - Sea Grant Program (Box 45)
    - Security Offices (Box 45)
    - Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs (Box 45)
    - Senate Assembly (Box 45)
    - Social Research, Institute for (Box 45)
    - Social Work, School of (Box 45)
    - Sociology (Box 45)
    - South and Southeast Asian Studies, Center for (Box 45)
    - Speech, Communication and Theater (Box 45)
    - State and Community Relations (Box 45)
    - Student Services, Office of (Box 45)
    - Student Organizations, Office of (Box 45)
    - Student Publications (Box 45)
    - Survey Research Center (Box 45)
    - Unions (Box 45)
    - University Activities Center (Box 45)
    - University Housing (Box 45)
    - University Musical Society (Box 45)
    - University of Michigan (General) (Box 45)
    - University of Michigan Press (Box 45)
    - University Relations (Box 45)
    - University Theatre Program (Box 45)
    - Willow Run Airport (Box 45)
    - Women-Affirmative Action Program (Box 45)
    - WUOM Radio Station (Box 45)
  - 1974
    - Academic Affairs, Office of Vice President for (Box 46)
    - Admissions, Office of (Box 46)
    - Aerospace Engineering Department (Box 46)
    - Affirmative Action Program (Box 46)
    - Afro-American and African Studies (Box 46)
    - Alumni Association (Box 46)
    - Anatomy (Med.) (Box 46)
    - Anthropology (LSA) (Box 46)
    - Appropriations (Box 46)
    - Architecture and Urban Planning, College of (Box 46)
    - Army Officer Education Program (Box 46)
    - Art, School of (Box 46)
    - Astronomy (LSA) (Box 46)
    - Athletics, Intercollegiate (1974-1976) (Box 46)
    - Atmospheric and Oceanic Science (Box 46)
    - Automotive Engineering Lab (Box 46)
    - Bands (Box 46)
    - Bio-Sciences (Box 46)
    - Biological Station (Box 46)
    - Botanical Gardens (Box 46)
    - Budget (Box 46)
    - Buildings (Box 46)
    - Business Administration, School of (Box 46)
    - Career Planning and Placement (Box 46)
    - Chemical Engineering (Box 46)
    - Chemistry (LSA) (Box 46)
    - Chinese Studies, Center for (Box 47)
    - Civil Engineering (Box 47)
    - Classical Studies (Box 47)
    - Clements Library, William L. (Box 47)
    - Commencement (Box 47)
    - Commission for Women (Box 47)
    - Committee on Institutional Cooperation (Box 47)
    - Continuing Education of Women, Center for (Box 47)
    - Continuing Legal Education, Institute of (Box 47)
    - Cook, W.W., Lectures (Box 47)
    - Dearborn Campus (Box 47)
    - Dentistry, School of (Box 47)
    - Dermatology (Box 47)
    - Detroit Area Study (Box 47)
    - Development Office (Box 47)
    - Economic Development, Center for Research on (Box 47)
    - Economics (LSA) (Box 47)
    - Education, School of (Box 47)
    - Electrical and Computer Engineering (Box 47)
    - Engineering, College of English (LSA) (Box 47)
    - Enrollment (Box 47)
    - Ethics and Religion, Office of (Box 47)
    - Exhibit Museum (Box 47)
    - Extension Service (Box 47)
    - Faculty (Box 47)
    - Fees (Box 47)
    - Financial (Box 47)
    - Financial Aid, Student, Office of (Box 47)
    - Flint College (Box 48)
    - Food Day, 1975 (Box 48)
    - Fresh Air Camp (Box 48)
    - Geography (LSA) (Box 48)
    - Geological Science (Box 48)
    - Gerontology, Institute of (Box 48)
    - Graduate Studies, Horace H. Rackham School of (Box 48)
    - Grants and Contracts (State and Federal) (Box 48)
    - Great Lakes and Marine Waters Center (Box 48)
    - Great Lakes Research Division (Box 48)
    - Health Service (Box 48)
    - Higher Education, Center for the Study of (Box 48)
    - Highway Safety Research Institute (Box 48)
    - History (LSA) (Box 48)
    - History of Art (LSA) (Box 48)
    - Hometown Stories (Box 48)
    - Honors
      - (Faculty) (Box 48)
      - (Student) (Box 48)
    - Hopwood Awards (Box 48)
    - Hospital Administration, Bureau of and Program in (Box 48)
    - Human Genetics (Box 48)
    - Human Growth and Development, Center for (Box 48)
    - Human Performance Center (Box 48)
    - Humanities (Eng.) (Box 48)
    - Industrial and Operations Engineering (Box 48)
    - Information Services (Box 48)
    - Interlochen (Box 48)
    - Japanese Studies, Center for (Box 48)
    - Journalism (LSA) Judiciary (Box 48)
    - Labor and Industrial Relations (Box 48)
    - Law School (Box 48)
    - Learning and Teaching, Center for Research on (Box 48)
    - Legislature (Michigan) (Box 48)
    - Libraries (Box 48)
    - Library Science, School of (Box 48)
    - Literature, Science and the Arts, College of, 2 folders (Box 48)
    - Management and Education, Division of (Box 48)
    - Materials and Metallurgical Engineering (Box 48)
    - Mathematics (LSA) (Box 48)
    - Mechanical Engineering (Box 48)
    - Media Resources (Box 48)
    - Medical School (Box 48)
    - Mental Health Research Institute (Box 48)
    - Mental Retardation and Related Disabilities, Institute for the Study of (Box 48)
    - Michigan Historical Collections (Box 48)
    - Michigan Men's Glee Club (Box 48)
    - Michigan Union (Box 48)
    - Minority Groups (Box 48)
    - Museum of Anthropology (Box 48)
    - Museum of Art (Box 48)
    - Music, School of (Box 49)
    - Natural Resources, School of (Box 49)
    - Naval Architecture and Marine Engineering (Box 49)
    - Near Eastern and North African Studies, Center for (Box 49)
    - Near Eastern Studies (Box 49)
    - Nuclear Engineering (Box 49)
    - Nursing, School of (Box 49)
    - Opportunity Award Program (Box 49)
    - Orientation, Office of (Box 49)
    - Personnel (Box 49)
    - Pharmacy, College of (Box 49)
    - Phoenix Project (Box 49)
    - Physical Education (Box 49)
    - Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation (Box 49)
    - Physical Properties, Department of (Box 49)
    - Physics (Box 49)
    - Poison Control Center (Box 49)
    - Political Science (Box 49)
    - Political Studies, Center for (ISR) (Box 49)
    - Postgraduate Medicine (Box 49)
    - President, Office of (Box 49)
    - Professional and Administrative Staff Services, Office of (Box 49)
    - Psychiatry (Box 49)
    - Psychology (LSA) (Box 49)
    - Public Health, School of (Box 49)
    - Public Policy Studies, Institute of (Box 49)
    - Regents (Box 49)
    - Registrar, Office of the (Box 49)
    - Research, Office of the Vice-President (Box 49)
    - Residential College (Box 49)
    - ROTC (General) (Box 49)
    - Russel, Henry, Lecture Awards (Box 49)
    - Russian and East European Studies, Center for (Box 49)
    - School Services, Bureau of (Box 49)
    - Science and Technology, Institute of (Box 49)
    - Sea Grant Program (Box 49)
    - Security Offices (Box 49)
    - Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs (Box 49)
    - Slavic Languages and Literature (Box 49)
    - Social Research, Institute for (Box 49)
    - Social Work, School of (Box 49)
    - Sociology (Box 49)
    - Speech Clinic (Box 49)
    - Speech, Communication and Theater (Box 49)
    - State and Community Relations (Box 49)
    - State Relations and Planning (Box 49)
    - Student Activities (Box 49)
    - Student Services, Office of (Box 49)
    - Student Organizations, Office of (Box 49)
    - Student Publications (Box 49)
    - Surgery, Department of (Box 49)
    - Survey Research Center (Box 49)
    - Television Center (Box 49)
    - Unions (Box 49)
    - University Activities Center (Box 49)
    - University Center for Adult Education (Box 49)
    - University Housing (Box 49)
    - University Musical Society (Box 49)
    - University of Michigan (General) (Box 49)
    - University of Michigan Press (Box 49)
    - University Relations (Box 49)
    - University Theatre Program, 2 folders (Box 49)
    - Utilization of Scientific Knowledge, Center for Research on (Box 49)
    - Visitors (Box 49)
    - Willow Run Airport (Box 49)
    - Women-Affirmative Action Program (Box 49)
    - Women's Study Program (Box 49)
    - WUOM Radio Station (Box 49)
  - 1975
    - Academic Affairs, Office of Vice President for (Box 54)
    - Admissions, Office of (Box 54)
    - Aerospace Engineering Department (Box 54)
    - Affirmative Action Program (Box 54)
    - Afro-American and African Studies (Box 54)
    - Alumni Association (Box 54)
    - Anatomy (Med.) (Box 54)
    - Anthropology (LSA) (Box 54)
    - Applied Mechanics and Engineering Science (Box 54)
    - Appropriations (Box 54)
    - Architecture and Urban Planning, College of (Box 54)
    - Art, School of (Box 54)
    - Astronomy (LSA) (Box 54)
    - Atmospheric and Oceanic Science (Box 54)
    - Automotive Engineering Lab (Box 54)
    - Bands (Box 54)
    - Bio-Sciences (Box 54)
    - Biological Station (Box 54)
    - Botanical Gardens (Box 54)
    - Budget (Box 54)
    - Buildings (Box 54)
    - Business Administration, School of (Box 54)
    - Career Planning and Placement (Box 54)
    - Chemical Engineering (Box 54)
    - Chemistry (LSA) (Box 54)
    - Chinese Studies, Center for (Box 54)
    - Civil Engineering (Box 54)
    - Clements Library, William L. (Box 54)
    - Commencement (Box 54)
    - Commission for Women (Box 54)
    - Committee on Institutional Cooperation (Box 54)
    - Computer and Communications Sciences (Box 54)
    - Computing Center (Box 54)
    - Continuing Education of Women, Center for (Box 54)
    - Continuing Legal Education, Institute of (Box 54)
    - Cooley, Thomas, Lectures (Box 54)
    - Dearborn Campus (Box 54)
    - Dental Research Institute (Box 54)
    - Dentistry, School of (Box 54)
    - Development Office (Box 54)
    - Economics (LSA) (Box 54)
    - Education, School of (Box 54)
    - Electrical and Computer Engineering (Box 54)
    - Engineering, College of (Box 54)
    - English (LSA) (Box 54)
    - English Language Institute (Box 54)
    - Enrollment (Box 54)